Friends, in this video you will learn how to get
two wheeler insurance using the PhonePe application, that is, let's
assume that
your security or bike
insurance is about to expire or
you have to renew it or it has expired, then
how will you be
able to get the insurance done sitting at home in just two minutes, along with this, watch the video carefully
and completely because guys, if you are
watching the whole thing carefully, then here I will
tell you one of my secret tips where
you will be able to get a very good insurance by paying the least amount of money, where
you will get to
see a lot of benefits here, you will
see the benefits and at the same time, guys,
you
can also increase the value of your vehicle here, so
understand the video carefully and completely,
open PhonePe on your mobile phone,
if you have not downloaded PhonePe yet, then
in the description of the video you will get the link of PhonePe app,
you can download it directly from there,
after that friends, you have to log in with your mobile number
and you have to
log in here in that way and
Here you will see insurance on the home page
and there are many types
of insurance below it like bike insurance, car
insurance, health insurance. So right now we have to get
insurance for our scooter bike, that is, for all our two wheelers, so for that
we have to click on the bike. Now guys,
here you will see that right now I had already
entered my vehicle number here.
If you do it for the first time, then
this is how the interface will appear in front of you. Now you have to
enter your two wheeler number here and after that
you have to submit it here. On submitting, it will
automatically appear in front of you that
which company your vehicle belongs to, which model it is
and when it was registered here.
Apart from this, here you are being asked
whether your insurance policy has
expired for more than 90 days.
If it has expired for more than 90 days, then you will say yes.
If it has not, then you will say no. So,
ours has expired now,
we have said yes to it.
After that guys, you have to view it here. As
you view, what is in front of you is
here.  But first of all you will be asked for the plan
that which plan you want to take, if
you click on it then you will
see three types of plans here
and it is possible that you may see only two
types of plans here, the reason for this friends is that the
first plan is
comprehensive, it is first party as well as
third party and the second one is
third party, this means that if
you cause an accident to someone's car
and the other person suffers loss
and you also suffer, then in this condition
if you have third party insurance then
here the insurance policy company will
only give the claim to the other party here, it will
not give it to you at all,
you will have to pay the loss yourself,
apart from this here is on damage on
damage, it means that if your
car is insured for 5 years and the
first year's insurance is
first party, that is,
everything is covered in it, but after that the
4 year insurance is
of third party and if you want that
after one year  If you want to get your first party insurance done in the second year as well, then
you have to choose the options here,
you have to take the on-damage plan
and you get this plan at a very low rate.
Now friends, do one thing,
tell me in the comments
which company's insurance you were using till now
and which scooter or bike you have.
Please do tell me by commenting. Now friends,
I would recommend you to always get your
comp insured here.
Everything is covered in it. So,
like we chose this, now it is being asked here whether
you want to do insurance for 1 year,
2 years or 3 years, so you can
select it, like we want to do it for one year only, there is no
problem. Now,
many companies have come here,
different companies are listed here and
see here, if you
also want personal accident cover, then you can turn
it on here and it will get
added to this. So, for now, we do not
need personal accident cover here.  There are
many different companies,
their pricing
is also different here and one thing you have to keep in mind is
that here your vehicle has an IDV
value, it means insured
declared value, now suppose your
vehicle catches fire or your vehicle gets stolen,
then in that condition
how much money will the insurance policy give you, that is,
if we take insurance of ₹ 7728 for 1 year, then
here the
company will give us a claim of ₹ 1 and apart from this,
here we are getting less IDV value of 871,
so this means that you can
compare here as per your understanding,
you have to choose the one which you think is best,
like according to me this company is
Digit, so here I will select it, bye,
now friends, you have to
review the details once, that is, you have to
check that you have entered the vehicle number
correctly, apart from that
your name will automatically appear here and
come here and click on it, now you will
see the third party here
How much money has been taken on damage,
how much is the GST and what is the total amount here,
let us get it done, now
you have to click on Buy Plan here,
now whatever your bank account
is linked here will come in this way, if you
want to make payment through debit card or credit card, then you will be able to link it here as well, for
now if we have to do it
through UPI, then we will click on Pay here,
now whatever is your UPI PIN,
you will enter it here and after that
you will have to submit it here, after submitting you
will see that our payment here has been
successfully completed,
after the payment is completed, you have to keep in mind that it is
very important to get KYC done here
because some time ago the Government has made it
compulsory here, so
you simply have to
click on Start KYC here, now you have to
enter your PAN number here
and whatever is your date of birth,
you have to enter it here,
we have filled up the details, after that we will do it
here  But submit, now you have to wait a little here,
after that another
page will open in front of you, now you can see that
another page has opened here and it is being
told here that KYC is in
process, this means that your
KYC has gone to the company,
whichever company you had taken insurance from, will
check it and verify it here,
now you will have to wait for 10 to 15 minutes,
after that you have to come back and
open the PhonePe application and
go to the insurance column here and you have to select the bike here,
after selecting, you
will see that our insurance is visible here,
so you simply have to
click on it here, after clicking, you will
see that your policy will automatically appear
here, you will simply
see an option to download the policy document, so
you have to download it here, as you
download here, you
can also take a printout of it directly and if you
want, if you want to
save it in your phone, then you can save it here
whatsapp2 If you want to get an insurance policy at the lowest price, then
friends, I have been getting
my scooter bike insured
from Ekko company for the last five to six years continuously because here you get a
very low price
and the IDV value of your vehicle is the
highest and apart from this, you get to
see many benefits if you
also want to get insurance from the company, then
how to do it,
you will get the link in the description of the video or
you will get it on the i button above, you
must watch that video and apart from this, let me make one
more thing clear to you, whenever you get
insurance done through the Phone Pay app and
you ever have to claim your insurance, let's say
your car gets
damaged somewhere and you have to claim it, then for this
you do not have to call on Phone Pay,
rather you have to
go to the policy customer number of the company whose insurance policy you have and you have to make a
call there and lodge your complaint
and claim your insurance, so in
this way you can do it very easily
You will be able to get insurance through the Phone Pay app. How did you like the video?
Please like the video and share it with your friends.